Yes, yes. How's it looking?
Oh, my God!
It is here, bruv.
This is insane.
I can't believe
this is actually happening. Yes.
- What's it saying?
- Oh, bruv, it's beautiful.
Dude, how many months
of selling underwear did you have to do
to afford the new wheel? Be honest.
I just know this means
you'll be at the gaming cafe less.
Yeah, bruv, I'm bored of the cafe.
Yo, I'm 99% sure
that I've beaten every single person
that's ever stepped foot in the cafe.
Also, for your information,
it only took me a month
of saving up at the knickers store
to afford the new wheel.
Not months, plural. Month, singular.
Moment of truth.
Oh, she's perfect.
This is so much better than my old setup.
I'm sorry, I'm unstoppable now.
I'm unstoppable.
All right, Big Dog.
I'm looking at Rory right now
and he says to meet in the lobby.
Race Le Mans. Yeah?
Fine. I'll play Rory.
- Jann.
- But tell him to bring his own coffin.
Jann.
Hey. Sorry, Dad.
We're headed to the field.
You wanna get outside
and kick it around a bit?
Get some air? It'll do you good.
No, I'm okay.
Sooner or later you're gonna have
to leave this room, right?
Dad! Come on, let's go!
You could learn from your younger brother.
If you'd practise football half as much
as you play this damn game--
I don't like football, Dad.
We've been over this.
'Sup, man, you still there?
Yeah.
Jeez, your dad's not into your lifestyle,
my bro.
God, yeah, no shit.
Bruv, I'm just gonna do
a quick custom job.
Where'd you go?
Janny.
Janny, where'd you go?
Sorry, I'm just adjusting the rear wing.
Giving it more downforce. More rake.
Janny, Rory's waiting.
Sorry, this car is ridiculous.
At this point this is actually a waste
of my time, but you know what?
Go on, I'll play Rory. Why not?
- The anticipation is killing me, bruv.
- I'm loading him into the Le Mans race.
Okay.
- Ready.
- Go, Speed Racer.
Let's go.
Hi. Good to see you again.
How may I help you, sir?
I'm Danny Moore with Marketing.
I have a meeting with Motorsports.
- Yes. Perfect. Here is your pass, sir.
- Thank you so much.
Well, thank you again for having me.
This is Yamauchi Kazunori,
creator of Gran Turismo,
a racing game so accurate...
it's inspired a love of driving
in 80 million players.
The realism, the physics,
the fidelity of the cars.
And recreated
the world's most famous racetracks
with meticulous attention to detail.
They test these cars over and over again.
All of this comes together
to give the player
the most realistic driving experience.
So when I came to Nissan...
my job was...
to call people who defaulted
on their car payments.
Most of them said,
"Go ahead, take it. I don't want it."
They'd rather be on their phones
in the back of an Uber
than driving themselves.
Car buyers today don't dream
of the open road.
They don't associate their cars
with adventure.
But Gran Turismo players do.
This is an untapped demographic of buyers
that we should be reaching.
And how do you suggest we do that?
By creating a contest
that offers the best video game players
in the world a chance
to compete in professional racing.
If we can take one driver
from the virtual world,
from behind their console,
and put them into a race car, onto a track
and turn them into a champion...
Nissan will reignite the dream to drive
in 80 million others.
Thank you.
Mr Moore.
You left these upstairs.
You really believe
one of these players could compete.
I do. Absolutely, yeah.
I've played the game
and it's remarkable, actually.
You understand if we put them in our cars
and somebody was hurt,
we would all be responsible.
Yes, I understand. Yes. Yeah.
The board has agreed to move forward
with your programme under one condition.
You find a certified chief engineer
to ensure that it's safe.
There can be no mistakes.
Absolutely. Of course.
I wish you luck.
Thank you.
Holy shit.
Yeah, of course I understand.
It is. It's a very steep learning curve.
But with the right instructor,
you know, like you...
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Thank you again for your time.
Holy shit.
Jack Salter.
Jack.
Jack!
Salter!
Got a visitor. Make it quick.
Capa wants that fixed yesterday.
It's a contest.
The fastest SIM racers in the world...
get to compete in a camp.
And the winner gets to race
for Team Nissan.
Wow. What do you get out of this?
You get a bigger office or something?
I wish.
It's insane. It's not gonna work.
It's far too dangerous.
Why?
You really think
that you're gonna put some kid
who's been playing a game in his bedroom
into a 200-mile-an-hour rocket?
It'll tear him to pieces.
These players have clocked more track time
than you have in your entire career.
On, what do you call it, a console?
You know that if you get in a wreck
out here, you can't hit reset, right?
How many guys you go to
before you went to me?
- A few.
- Yeah. "A few."
A lot.
But nobody
with your particular experience.
Oh, God. Come on, man.
I haven't been chief engineer in 15 years.
These kids, they're outsiders too.
I know it's unprecedented,
but so was a kid from Iowa racing Le Mans.
Yeah. Look how that turned out.
Don't you wanna take racing back
from these pricks
who think they can just buy it?
I'm talking about a chance
to compete again.
Don't you want one last shot?
I think
those days are in my rearview, friend.
Then what are you doing here?
Somewhere out there, there's a kid
who's faster than all these assholes...
that's just never gotten a chance
to show the world what they're capable of.
I'm gonna find them!
Yeah, cool.
Here we go.
Oh, yum, get excited.
Lentil salad. My favourite.
- No sarcasm at the table, please.
- No having fun at the table, please.
You're a dedicated athlete.
Diet matters. Yeah? Eat up.
You're starting on the wing tomorrow.
Plenty of eyes on you.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
When I go pro,
I'll eat at a steakhouse every night.
You'll be there too, Jann.
You could be our waiter.
Very funny.
But I'm not gonna be a waiter.
I've got plans.
Says the dude who sells stockings
at the department store.
- Coby.
- Coby, that's enough.
- On a roll tonight.
- Okay.
Have you thought at all
about going back to university?
Mum, we've been over this so many times.
Motorsports Engineering is a step
in that direction.
And I told you, at university,
they didn't let us drive the cars.
Not again about the race cars.
Didn't you say
"Always do something you love"?
Yes. Yes. I did,
but I meant within the realm of reality.
I played grassroots football for years
before my first professional contract.
Well, I can start at the bottom.
Work in the pits. Do car maintenance.
Yeah, but that's not our world, son.
- You know what racing cars cost?
- It's what I love.
It's what I'm good at.
These lentils are quite nice.
I'm not hungry.
Throughout my life,
I've invested in talent
that guarantees me
a front-row seat to greatness,
and this is what we endeavour towards
this season.
To be elite.
No? Nicky, my boy,
last year we had a rough start.
But this year,
everything from the cars to the team
will be best in class.
This year will be our greatest.
Hear, hear.
This season is going to be great,
but it comes down to dedication.
Talent.
So no messing around. I'll demand
as much from you as I do of myself,
so make sure you keep up or you're gone.
Nick, you looked good out there today.
You have something to say?
You're not carrying enough speed
into turn four.
You know that, right? You're braking early
and you should push it.
Oh, you're giving me advice right now?
You're a good driver, Nick.
I don't know how many times
you need to hear that.
But you get a little emotional.
And when you get emotional--
You're a mechanic.
If I want driving advice,
I'll talk to my team leader.
Not some flamed-out has-been
who couldn't back it up 50 years ago.
Hello, you've reached the voicemail
of Danny Moore. Leave a message.
Tell Nissan I'll do it.
I'm not spending another minute
with this pretentious clown show.
I'll teach your gamer kids how to drive.
They just gotta prove to me
that they can do it.
If I feel like it's unsafe,
I'm gonna walk.
Not gonna have blood on my hands.
How we doing, gamers?
My favourite sound in the world.
Sound of clicking. How we doing, brother?
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
Excuse me.
- Can I get your help here, please?
- Yes. Of course you can.
Hey.
You are joking.
Bruv, you gotta see this.
Dude, I've only got a minute. What's up?
Dude.
- What is this?
- I saw this message on the screen.
It says that the account
that was last logged in on this console
got one of the fastest lap times
in the UK.
Dude, it was your account.
- Wait, this is a joke.
- No. It's a contest.
Press play, dude.
If you're one of the very, very few people
getting this message,
it means that you set
the fastest lap time in Gran Turismo.
There's a virtual race happening tomorrow.
Win it and a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity awaits you.
We've created an academy
to take the best SIM racers in the world
and train them to race real race cars.
We want to prove to the whole world
that the impossible dream can happen.
Dude, this is real?
It's as real as a ten-car pileup
on the M4. Bad example.
You need to practise now.
- Why don't you follow the race line?
- Just experimenting.
See, the other drivers,
they follow that line.
So if I go wide like this,
sometimes I beat them.
Like that.
And if it doesn't work, I just reset.
Night-night, son.
Night, Dad.
If you're getting this message,
it means that you're one
of the best Gran Turismo players
in the world right now.
What?
Looking at porn?
- No. I'm not.
- Liar.
Come on.
We're throwing a party at the pier.
Dude, you took the keys?
Coby, you're on your last strike.
Mum will kill you if you get in trouble.
That's why we're using your window.
Sorry, man. I've gotta practise.
I heard Audrey will be there.
Come on.
Coby, give me the keys.
Nope.
Let me drive.
I'm a better driver, bruv.
This is bullshit, Coby.
I can't believe I'm letting you drive.
I can't believe I invited you.
Get in, Jann.
You better not screw up Dad's car.
Drop the clutch.
I thought you could drive.
Cheers, bruv.
Simulate me, Janny!
Hey.
You having fun over here?
Yeah, I was coming over in a sec.
Yeah?
We were just talking about travelling.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I don't know, do you ever just...
wanna pack a bag
and leave here and never look back?
All the time.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
Me too.
You know, if there was one place
in the world that I could go,
I think it would be New York.
Why?
I've heard they have good pizza.
Yes. I've heard that too.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What about you?
This is stressful.
Gun to your head, what's one place
you wanna go before you die?
Tokyo. Done.
- Okay. Tokyo.
- Tokyo.
Is that because of the guy
who created your game?
Yes, but technically it's not a game.
I mean,
technically it's a racing simulator.
Right. Okay.
Sorry.
What is it about racing
that you love so much?
Well...
Sometimes when I'm driving,
I can be going so fast,
and everything else is moving so slow,
and it's like the rest of the world
just falls away.
It's just you and the car...
and that's it.
It's kind of magic.
Magic.
Put out the fire!
Put it out!
- I should probably get going.
- Yeah.
My train leaves early.
I bet Brighton is better than here.
Yes. It is.
DM me sometime, Jann.
I'll be watching for you.
Good luck with the simulating.
- Bye.
- Thank you. Bye.
Audrey, let's go!
Oh, come on!
You drive slower
than my grandmother! Let's go!
Yeah, well, there's a reason
that I'm driving.
I'm the sober one. Chill.
Let's see if these guys got a beer for me.
Hey!
You got more beers there?
Are you still thirsty, mate? I got you!
Couple o' pints on me!
You are kidding me.
Oh, sit down. Stop.
I'm done. Like, finished!
The uni captain will pull my scholarship--
Yo, shut up, shut up.
Shush, shush, shush.
All right, belts on. Get your belt on.
My football career's over.
What are we gonna do?
We'll spend the night in jail
if they catch us now.
Jail?
No, what? No, we can't.
Shut up!
They're pulling them over, not us.
I'm not missing my race tomorrow.
What the bloody hell are you doing?
Oh, Jesus Christ!
- I'm gonna puke.
- Yo, don't puke in my dad's car.
Jann!
Be chill, be chill, be chill.
Have they gone?
Yes, we're not going to jail!
Bollocks. Oh, man.
He'll know I was drinking if you drove.
- He could tell my coach.
- He's not telling him nothing.
He wants you on the team
more than you wanna be on the team.
Okay, say I'm the better driver
and I'll take the blame.
Say I'm the better driver
and I'll take the blame. Say it.
- Say I'm the better driver. Say it.
- You're the better driver.
We couple the lead engine
with the cars, yeah?
- Yes.
- Connect the rod.
The pneumatics.
Yep.
Release.
What's up? You in a hurry?
You got someplace to be?
- Sorry. No.
- Yeah. Bring that up.
Dad, obviously I'm happy to pay
for the damage to the mirror
and the paintwork and stuff,
but I was just wondering how many
of these sessions I have to do. You know?
You think that's why you're here?
Is it not?
You're not here
because you broke the mirror on the car,
or because you took it without asking me.
Then why am I here?
Because this is where you end up
when you don't have a plan.
I'm sorry, wait.
Am I here because I play Gran Turismo?
You think you're gonna play
stupid video games about cars
and you're gonna become a race car driver?
Either you go back to school
and find something achievable,
or you can join me here now.
But there's no future in racing.
I'm done.
Pick up, pick up.
- I'm coming.
- Dude, the race starts in two minutes.
I need you to sign me in.
I have signed you in, but it's
a rolling start. I can't control it.
If I'm not there when the lights go green,
start the race.
No. What? That's illegal, I can't do that.
- It's gotta be you that drives.
- If I don't get this, I'm done.
We are moments away from the start
of the European qualifying race.
Come on, come on, come on.
Bruv, it's starting. It's starting!
Best of luck to all you gamers out there.
Go, go, go!
Three, two, one...
And we're off!
- Can you catch up?
- I think so.
- Persol, how many am I up against?
- It is you against the 19 best in Europe.
Okay, bro, you're in 17th position,
but you got ten laps to come back.
We need a win
to go to GT Academy. Come on.
Loosey-goosey, baby. Loosey-goosey.
He's boxing you out.
You gotta do something.
Time's running out.
I'm taking the outside.
There's no time to dance.
Yes, Jann. That's my boy.
Two seconds back from the next car.
This is it. Last lap, you gotta go.
Come on, Jann!
- Okay, second position just spun out.
- Oh, shit!
I'm six seconds behind the leader.
Final turn now.
Come on, Jann.
Push it!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
That's him, that's him. There he is.
You'll let him walk out
without knowing who's operating this camp?
He's only off to Northampton.
He's off to race cars. Do you have
any idea how dangerous that is?
Dad, I'm sorry, you're the one that said,
"Go and do something real."
Now I am, and it's too dangerous.
Make up your mind.
Look, this has never
been done before, Jann.
It's a gimmick.
You've barely driven a real car.
Dad, I've raced thousands of hours.
But it's not the same, son.
Real drivers,
they're professional athletes. Not like--
Dad, do you remember this day?
You took this of me when I was 5.
All I've wanted to do since then
is be a racer.
I am doing it.
Whether you believe in me or not.
Welcome to the GT Academy.
Hi.
The ten of you...
hailing from eight different countries,
are the best SIM racers
in the world.
You've overcome incredible odds
to be here.
Now you stand on this track...
with enormous opportunity.
The winner will earn a seat
on Team Nissan...
and a place in racing history.
Now, please meet our chief engineer,
the man who's gonna teach you all
how to do it, Jack Salter.
Dude's a fricking legend.
So all these folks behind me are...
keen on y'all proving
you can do the impossible.
I'm here to prove that you can't.
Hi. What's your name?
Jann Mardenborough.
Jann. Wow, you're tall.
You fit in a race car?
I don't know.
I guess in the game I do.
This is not a game.
Racing.
It takes strength,
it takes tremendous will,
intelligence, sensitivity.
There's only a handful of people
in the entire world
who can do it at the level
that you're gonna be asked to do it.
When you're in a race,
the g-forces will be twice
what an astronaut experiences
upon liftoff.
And it's under these conditions
that you're gonna be forced
to make split-second decisions
that could cost you your life.
Or worse...
you could kill someone else.
These are incredible stakes.
And if you're not willing to risk it,
I want you to walk away.
There's absolutely no shame.
'Cause if you stay, I'm gonna push you
harder than you have ever been pushed,
and I am gonna prove
that you don't have what it takes.
Because to take one look at any of you,
I can already tell that you don't.
Welcome.
Great pep talk, Churchill.
I think they got the point.
Look.
This was my dream.
To take SIM racers,
put them into real cars,
and have them race
against professional drivers.
Now is your chance
to turn dreams into reality.
Let's go!
This is the first time
you've been in a race car,
as opposed to sitting
in front of a computer screen.
There's a lot of similarities
when it comes to throttle, braking.
How to take turns, how to use brakes,
find your line on the track.
I think this is the chance
we've all been looking for,
to become what we wanted to.
You never know how high you can achieve.
- Dreams can come true.
- All right, Jann.
- Jann?
- Yes.
And just remember this whole thing
is about press readiness, okay?
When did you know
that you wanted to be a racer?
Well, I liked cars since I was a kid.
Go, go, go. Come on.
You're going
to compete in different exercises
so that we can determine whose SIM skills
translate to driving a real car.
I wasn't prepared for just how physical
the demands of the car were gonna be.
-What do you think about your competitors?
- They're great.
How about Matty?
To each his own. He's obviously
very confident. Good for him.
What do you think about Jann?
Jann is the same as any other driver
on the track. Just another car to pass.
Matty with the answers.
Better strap in too, man.
We're about to go fast.
Let's see it.
We're gamers.
We're competitive people.
Let's go, keep it clean. Come on!
Oh, God.
This entire thing is
a marketing extravaganza.
Get in the chopper.
Let us get a few shots.
- Doing what?
- Follow the kids around the track,
make some notes,
act like an engineer, look cool.
There's no way I would evaluate
race car drivers from a helicopter.
It's the dumbest thing
I have ever heard in my whole life.
I'm not getting in that thing.
Looking good, Matty.
You're looking good on the straight there.
Nice line.
Come on, you gotta go. Punch it!
I will be your judge. I will be your jury.
All right, come on, you gamer kids.
This must be a new experience for you.
Last time you stretched your legs
was to go get another packet
of Hot Pockets from the freezer.
You get tired, you get sloppy.
You get sloppy, you get hurt.
Then you lose races!
I heard your trainer Jack can be
a little hard on the team.
I mean, he means it well.
He's tough, but it's like tough love.
I need you to be faster than this.
Don't think, just react.
You're gonna be hot in the car.
You're gonna be tired. Focus!
Jack thinks we just suck.
Grabbed a bunch of cones back there.
Extra points!
And I will decide who is eliminated.
Close that gap. Let's close that gap.
No, no, no, no!
No!
Jesus Christ.
Sorry about the car.
Good luck.
We'll cut you down to five.
Those five will compete in a final race.
Bye!
Keep going! Keep going!
If your name's below the red line
at the end of this, you're out.
You're ruining my enjoyment
of these chips.
Hello.
I didn't think it was gonna be
so physically demanding.
You puked on my lawn.
Goodbye, Henry.
No, no, no. Come on, come on!
Goodbye, Chloe.
I wasn't into sports and I didn't know
that we had so much working out.
Klaus.
Can I have a word?
Good effort, son.
Here's a cap and a shirt for you.
See that car? That'll take you home.
Bye, Klaus.
What's your biggest fear?
I guess going home
and proving everybody right.
You know, that...
that this, it was impossible
and this wasn't meant to be.
Passing is the art of conviction.
You're coming into turn 15.
It's got a late apex. The exit tightens.
You gotta find your moment to pass.
Come on. What you got? What you got?
Come on, there's a gap. Go, go, go.
Wait for the window.
Come on, turn it! Go! Go, go, go, go!
Not today.
- Brake! Brake!
- I'm trying!
Good night.
You okay?
Jesus Christ.
I braked.
Jesus.
But I braked. I braked, I braked.
- I'm so sorry.
- You can't be afraid in the car.
I wasn't afraid. I braked.
I don't know what happened.
Gotta commit!
You okay? You okay?
It work in your game?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Dude, you crashed a car with Jack inside.
That was insane.
Terrifying.
Listen, you gotta commit.
You know if you don't commit
in the turn, it's our lives on the line.
Uncanny.
I don't know if I was more scared
of the crash or of Jack.
- You actually got a bit lucky.
- Yeah, I think I did.
Clearly, I mean, you haven't been
behind the wheel before, have you?
No, I don't think any of us have.
The whole point is
to find someone who hasn't.
Well, I think
the point is to win. Isn't it?
Is there a problem?
I don't know. Is there?
I'm in first place, baby.
- He's humble too.
- Yeah.
But you heard Jack.
I mean, there's no shame
in going home, right?
- Yeah, did you hear that?
- That's exactly what I heard.
If you're not gonna commit to a pass...
If you, in the moment,
you decide, "I'm not gonna go"...
I mean, you gotta fall back,
you gotta brake early...
I tried. The brakes didn't respond.
Excuse me?
I tried to brake and the brakes didn't--
Brakes not working?
That's not what I said.
But I felt like they were glazed.
Oh, they were glazed. Yeah.
They were glazed.
How do you know?
How do you know something like that?
'Cause I've been driving
these cars for years.
In a video game.
We're in real life now, okay?
This is reality.
If you're not gonna commit,
if you're not gonna have conviction
on that track...
you make mistakes like that,
next time we might not be so lucky.
That's it. Get out.
Why do you think we're here?
Because we know how these cars work.
I know what I'm talking about.
I'm not afraid.
Come on, man.
Been doing this for 25 years.
I know when someone's afraid.
Best-case scenario, that guy doesn't win.
And that's what we got here.
There's no shame in that. It's okay.
It's a small percentage of the population
that can do this, all right?
I get it.
But it's time to quit.
If those brakes don't turn out
to be glazed,
you're going home anyways.
He was right. The brakes are glazed.
Hey.
How'd you know that about the car?
I've spent hours setting up cars in GT.
You know, I know you think
it's just a simulator, but it's good.
Tomorrow's your shot.
Marcel's out.
You're in the final five.
Final race in the morning.
Yes!
Do you hear this?
Yeah.
Dude.
- Jann.
- What?
What the hell is that?
It's Kenny G.
Who's Kenny G?
Dude, we have a huge race tomorrow.
It's just chilling me out.
I'll turn it down.
Sorry.
Dude.
All right. This is it.
This is what it's all been leading to.
This is not a game.
This is a race.
All your weeks here at the GT Academy
have led to this,
and I've imparted to you
everything I know about racing.
Now it's time for you
to show me what you've got
and what kind of competitors you are.
There will be a winner.
And there will be...
losers.
Good luck.
It's a...
It's a family thing.
It's the team my dad used to play for.
It's just a game.
Course is green. Track is all clear.
All cars on the grid.
Safety vehicles released to the track.
You're playing a game. It's just a game.
When in doubt, throttle out.
You got this.
These cars are heavy and fast.
Control those vehicles.
Yes!
No!
Yes. Yes!
Completed lap 2.
Three laps to go.
Those are nice splits.
Try harder, Jann.
Damn it!
Yes.
Oh, there you are. Okay.
This is it. Final lap.
Come on, Jann.
Commit.
Commit!
Okay, you came to drive, Stretch!
No.
No!
No! No.
Come on, Jann.
Come on, Matty. Do it, baby. Come on.
Yes. Come on.
- Matty took it.
- No, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, hang on, hang on.
We gotta watch that back.
Can I get playback?
Guys.
Was that me that--?
Did I win? Who had that?
Mate, who won?
I don't know. I don't know.
Rewind a little.
Zoom in there.
No. Mardenborough won.
- Announce it.
- Hold on. Hold on.
Jack. Jack.
Is this really what we want?
Just look at this from
a high-level marketing perspective, okay?
Does Jann give us the best shot?
I don't know what that means. He won.
By a thousandth of a second.
Yeah, that's the difference
between winning and losing. Jann won.
Jann...
Look, he stumbles in front of the camera.
He's not press-ready. He's not confident.
The whole idea of this thing, Jack,
it hangs on one
of these two kids' shoulders.
Matty's a millionth of a second behind.
I mean, who cares?
He is ultimately our best pick
when you take him out into the world.
- Who won?
- Right.
Yep. Copy that.
The winner is...
- You are the winner.
- Yes!
Way to go, Jann!
Well, and so it begins.
- Hello, sweetheart.
- Mum.
I kind of won GT Academy.
Really? That's amazing. I'm happy for you.
Yeah, it was amazing.
It was incredible.
You would have loved it.
- I wish you were here.
- I wish I was there too.
Where's Dad? I wanna tell him.
He's just left for Coby's game.
But I'll let him know.
I'm really proud of you.
Yeah. It's mental.
Yeah, they're taking me
on a Learjet to Vienna tomorrow.
I'll be watching.
And I love you.
I love you, bye.
A little bit of bubbly.
First time on a private jet.
Here, have a glass.
- Sweet. Thanks.
- Ah, sorry.
Champagne is for the podium only.
We'll take a couple beers.
Thank you very much.
That's fair. Let's save it for a win.
Nissan has agreed to fund you
through the Dubai enduro,
under the condition
you get your racing licence.
So we'll start in the European series.
You following?
Yes.
You've gotta finish fourth place or better
in just one race of the series
to get your FIA licence.
When you get that licence,
Nissan will give you a contract.
You're not gonna be racing against gamers.
These guys are
legit professional athletes.
You don't have
the strength and the stamina
to compete at this level at this point,
but we'll get into all that.
For this one, though,
you gotta prove that you belong.
And nobody's gonna welcome you
into this world.
The other drivers, your pit crew,
nobody wants you there.
If you have any feedback about anything,
you're gonna tell me.
'Cause the mechanics are going
to hate you.
Okay.
I'm gonna get some sleep
'cause I can't stand flying.
Get some rest.
He's fun.
Seriously...
Jack was a great racer.
I mean, possibly...
could have been one of the best Americans
of his generation, actually.
He quit.
Why?
Well, that's between you and him.
Yes.
Welcome to Vienna, Jann.
Welcome to Spielberg in Austria
at The Red Bull Ring.
This one's got a bit of everything.
Heavy braking zones
but also a lot of fast sections.
I'll be on comms the whole time.
You'll be fine. Stay with me.
Good news. No one thinks we can do this,
so low expectations.
Hey.
You got this.
- Blankets off.
- Copy.
Comms check.
Yeah, got you.
All right, it's a rolling start.
Let's get those tyres nice and warm.
They're trying to generate as much heat
in the tyres as they possibly can.
I don't know exactly how much bandwidth
you have for this right now,
but I feel like we should talk
about some of the players
on the field today.
First of all, my favourite is the guy
in the gold lamé monstrosity over there.
That's Team Capa.
The guy in the white Audi
with the rainbows on it, that's Schulin.
He's gonna be the other bully
on the track today.
I think the thing you have to remember--
This is a first, a world first,
so we're already winning.
You gotta have nerves of steel
coming down into turn one,
as we approach the start line.
Okay, Jann, when that light turns green,
it's go time.
Green, green! Go, go, go!
All right, come on,
keep your nose in it. Let's do this.
Whoa, welcoming committee.
- On your left!
- What the--? Shit.
You're all right.
You're all right. Just breathe.
- Just breathe.
- Okay, come on, Jann.
Focus, focus, focus.
Let's go.
Heading into turn one,
they're tipping on 300 kilometres an hour.
Get out from behind him.
Take the inside! You'll be fine.
Cars explode all the time.
This is normal. Stay focused.
It's a disaster for the red Ferrari.
He's not used to this kind of stuff,
so he needs to focus.
Jack, how am I doing for fuel?
All right, low fuel.
Next time around, come in to gas up.
First pit stop
for Jann Mardenborough and Nissan.
Let's go, go, go!
Come on, come on!
It's much easier with a joystick,
isn't it?
Noob!
Hey, hey! Listen to me!
Keep it together out there, all right?
Breathe! I don't want you to oversteer!
I want you to keep it together!
That was pretty textbook
from the Nissan pit crew.
You've got a good run on him.
Pass him on the right.
Watch out for Nismo, coming up behind you!
No! You let him take the inside!
Shit! Damn gamer!
That's a great job
from Jann Mardenborough.
Hey. That was actually pretty great.
You're coming up on Capa.
He's right ahead.
Fourth place! All we gotta do is hold
and we got that licence.
Where do you think you're going, amateur?
All right, watch out for Capa.
He's coming on your outside.
This guy plays dirty. Watch out for that.
I'm gonna nerf you, gamer.
Four back. Three back.
Goddamn it.
So it's a P-27 over the line
for Jann Mardenborough.
Possible naivete through the final...
Well, at least you finished.
I didn't even think you'd do that.
Noob.
It's an okay start.
There's still six more events this season,
so we'll qualify, all right?
So how are we feeling?
Are you still happy about
the choice we made?
Gotta give him some time.
All right. It's on you.
I'm sorry, man.
It's okay. First race. First race.
Yeah.
Crazy out there, isn't it?
It's insane.
All right, well...
We're gonna focus on strength,
we're gonna focus on endurance.
You're gonna feel better,
you're gonna feel stronger with each race.
Jack. Jack, hello? Is this working?
Jack! Hello? Jack! Hello.
Jack? Are you--?
Shit. I think my radio's broken.
Hello, Jack? Someone answer me!
I got a good feeling about this one.
You got this.
Another disappointing finish
for Mardenborough.
Come on. Run, run, run!
Look alive, look alive!
Hey, watch the gravel trap.
Nicholas, Nicholas! Nicholas!
What's your take on SIM racers?
I'm worried, you know? They make it
less safe for the real drivers.
Do you think a SIM racer can ever win?
You won't see them on a podium.
Okay, that's enough for now.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Come on.
Let us through, let us through.
Hey. Hey.
Don't worry about him, all right?
He's not a better driver than you.
He's got a bigger allowance.
Shit!
Whoa, don't let him take that line.
- Come on, he's pushing you wide.
- Bullshit.
Do it!
Whoopsie.
Shit!
The Dubai Autodrome, here in the UAE.
Is the car functioning all right?
Jann, is the car functioning okay?
Fine! The car's okay.
It's functioning, yes.
Okay. Okay, get back in the fight, then.
This is the last chance you have
to qualify for your licence.
We have to finish at least fourth.
You're still in this race.
Take a deep breath.
Focus.
I know you can do this, Jann.
Capa and Schulin are up ahead.
You're gaining back.
He's threading the needle
between Capa and Schulin.
You back for more?
Jack, what is he doing?!
Easy. Don't lose that line.
Don't lose that line.
Jack, they're boxing me in.
Well, then do something about it.
Hits the brakes, goes down to third!
What the--?
See you. Bye!
That's what I'm talking about!
Aw, shit!
Watch your six.
Oh, my God, he's gaining way
too much speed. What is he doing?
Shit! Capa's tyre just shattered
my windscreen.
Okay, pit now. Pit. Yellow's out.
Hey, you all right?
- Can you see through this thing?
- Yeah.
Are you okay? Come this way, please.
Let's get you checked. How do you feel?
The safety team arriving...
It is all clear for Nick Capa.
He's absolutely furious.
Stay calm, all right?
- Ready to go!
- All right. Green. Go!
Stay ahead of Schulin!
Racing once again.
And we're right into the final lap.
You gotta hold Schulin off.
You're in fourth place,
but you gotta play defence.
Do not let him get under you
in these turns.
This is it. Last turn and final straight.
- Drop the hammer!
- Roger that.
Will the German get the better
of the young rookie?
Watch that checkered flag!
- Yes!
- Fuck!
Whoa, fourth!
That's your FIA licence, kid.
Yes! Yes!
Yeah, baby!
Dude, what is your problem?!
It's part of the game. It's called racing.
Are you for real? You almost killed me!
You almost killed me!
Do that again and watch what happens.
Try that shit again. I'm serious.
You almost killed me and yourself!
I'm serious!
Hey! Hey! You came in fourth!
You came in fourth!
- FIA licence, baby!
- You got your licence!
You did it! You did it! Forget that guy.
You broke your cherry!
You got your licence!
Hey.
Got you a beer.
Thank you.
- So.
- Yes?
You were pretty damn good today.
- Don't sound so surprised.
- I am surprised.
I'm very surprised.
You got instincts. That can't be taught.
Did you feel it when you were out there?
That thing where time slows down,
and you feel like the car's on rails.
You feel like you can't make a mistake.
Feels like nothing and everything
at the same time.
Jesus, I miss that so much.
That's the only thing
I miss about being in the car.
Now I only get it when I, you know, listen
to early Black Sabbath or something.
Just, like, the bullshit fades away.
That's what you're listening to
on this thing?
- Black Sabbath?
- Yeah.
You know, they make these
that hold more than eight songs.
I'm nostalgic, what do you want?
Hey, what are you gonna do
with that big ol' signing bonus?
I don't know.
I'll probably put it towards a flat.
You're such a nerd.
Why don't you take a bunch of it
and blow it on a first-class ticket
for that girl you're obsessed with
and fly her out here
to be there
for the signing event with you.
I don't have a girl.
You don't have a girl?
Who's the girl that you're looking at,
like, hundreds of pictures
on your phone all day long?
Who's that girl?
- You rookie.
- Danny...
Danny told me
you were an incredible driver.
Yeah?
Yeah. What was your favourite track?
Le Mans. Hands down.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Why?
- It's a perfect track.
Nowhere tests you like that.
You podium at Le Mans
and you live forever.
- You become immortal.
- Did you?
No. I did not. I am still mortal.
But I did race it. Once.
What happened?
You're the racer from today, right?
Can we get your autograph?
Yeah, sure.
- You were amazing, by the way.
- Thank you so much.
Can I get a selfie as well?
- For sure.
- Thanks.
Jann. This is a surprise.
You know, I was just watching
your story on Insta.
Oh, really?
Well, that's crazy.
I was wondering how many times
I'd have to like them
before you'd call me.
Fifty, sixty times?
Yeah, sorry.
I should have called sooner, but--
It's okay. You've been busy.
I was thinking about
that night that you left and...
Yeah?
I wish we'd got more time, you know?
Jann, we have all the time in the world.
Where do you wanna go?
How is everybody?
It's an absolute honour to meet you, sir.
It took me a decade to prove
that Gran Turismo could work.
This young man has proven it
in just one year.
Jann.
By signing this contract
as a professional driver,
you're showing not only gamers...
but any kid who had a dream...
that anything is possible.
Welcome to Team Nissan.
This way!
- Jann-san. This way, please.
- Jann-san, please! Look this way.
Thank you so much. Thank you, thank you.
- Hey.
Hey.
Man of the hour.
- Yeah, you came.
- Thanks for bringing me here.
Do you have any time to enjoy Tokyo?
And what sights would you like to see?
Yeah, I would like to see more of Tokyo.
I would love to.
Guys, thank you so much. I think we've had
more than enough questions for now.
Now get out while you can, guys, go.
Quick, make a run for it. Enjoy the city.
You and me dreamed of this in Wales,
and now...
it's real.
We manifested this.
Yeah, maybe we did.
Oh, cool.
What are you looking at?
Might buy a gift for a friend.
Sake?
After you.
Or we could order something else.
What is there?
Champagne, maybe?
Celebrate your big signing?
Champagne's for the podium.
- Oh, okay.
- Sorry.
Noted, Mr Big Shot.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
That's amazing.
Man, that is amazing. That is so good.
More, more, more.
Most challenging circuit in the world.
So hard to remember.
It is the most feared circuit
on planet Earth.
It is, of course,
the Nürburgring Nordschleife.
Why don't you check out
those numbers over there, all right?
Hey.
It's time.
Yeah.
You okay?
Here.
What is this, my birthday?
It's just, I don't know, something I saw.
Open it later.
Have a good one, mate.
It's been an impressive start
to the season
for the young lad from Wales,
Jann Mardenborough,
who just a month ago
placed fourth at Dubai Autodrome.
He looks so young.
Yeah, the Nordschleife is
the most challenging circuit
and it's gonna be the biggest challenge
of Jann's career so far.
All clear. Drop the car.
You hear me in there?
Loud and clear.
Looking good, Jann. Smooth is fast.
Smooth is fast.
Very nice! Schulin down.
Showing fantastic pace
from Jann Mardenborough
as he's working his way up
through the field.
Pit for fuel when you come around.
Copy.
What the hell?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Was that his car?
Oh, no!
That is a terrifying accident
for Jann Mardenborough,
and all we can do at this moment
is hope he's okay.
We aren't sure of his condition.
May be still in the car.
But we hope
that he and the spectators are okay.
It's a horrible accident.
Hey, wait!
Stop, stop!
Oh, no. Oh, Jann.
My baby.
I don't know how we're gonna
explain this to Nissan.
There's got to be an investigation.
That's what
you're thinking about right now?
They could shut us down over this.
- Okay. Somebody died.
- I understand.
Hey.
No, whoa, whoa.
Hey. Come on.
You need to rest, you need to rest.
I'm okay.
What happened?
It's not your fault, okay?
It was a freak accident.
Was someone hurt?
A spectator.
Did they die?
It was an accident.
It is certainly not on you.
It is on me.
I should've pitted you sooner.
- Oh, my God.
- Hey.
You know why they call
that section Flugplatz?
It means "airfield."
Cars lift off there.
With that headwind, it was like a sail.
It was a freak accident, Jann.
Come on.
I shouldn't have been there.
Someone's dead
because racing is dangerous.
- I was driving.
- Jann, you can't be blamed for this.
Can you go? Can you go? I'm done.
Jann, listen to me, okay?
Get out!
I'd like to start
by saying everybody at Nissan
would like to extend their deepest
condolences to the family of the deceased.
This was a tragic accident,
and our hearts go out to them.
Do you want me to come down there?
I can.
That's okay.
I'm not much fun at the moment.
What about your family?
Have you spoken to them?
We are, of course,
cooperating with the investigation,
and we will provide racing officials
and the DMSB
with any information that would help
prevent this from happening again.
He should have never been on that track.
And you should have stayed
where you belong.
Under the hood.
The hospital said
you were discharged with no injuries.
Please let us come and see you.
I'm not sure if I can do this.
But, sweetheart,
you know it wasn't your fault, right?
This could've happened to anybody.
Yeah, but it happened to me.
Do you wanna speak to your dad? Or Coby?
What, so they can just say
they were right?
He just wants to know you're okay.
So do I, my baby.
Let's go.
You had asked me
what happened at Le Mans.
I was in a wreck.
It was a beautiful day.
It was getting late in that first day,
and I was coming out
of the Tertre Rouge corner.
I was coming up on a Ford.
As I passed him, I saw his car twitch.
It was like a shiver.
And then he lost control.
Car flipped three times
before it hit the barrier.
Caught on fire like that.
Medics came, pulled me out.
My gloves were on fire,
but everything else...
not a scratch.
But that Ford was in a thousand pieces.
Tony, the driver,
he died on the way to the hospital.
They said it wasn't my fault.
I never got behind the wheel
of a race car ever again.
I lost my nerve.
More than that, I lost the chance
to find out how good I could have been.
I quit.
I've had to live with that...
my whole life.
You wanna walk away...
nobody would blame you.
Most people would.
I got a feeling you're not most people.
I think you could be the best.
But if you wanna prove it,
if you wanna be a driver,
then you gotta get back on that track
and you gotta do it right now.
Because if you don't, you never will.
That crash is not gonna define
who you are.
But how you respond to it...
will.
Finish your lap.
All right, nice and easy.
- Just hold the line.
- Okay.
Give it a little speed.
Let's have some fun.
You're okay.
What's next?
The racing commission has finally
come to their decision.
Good news is they've cleared you.
Yeah, it's great news.
What's the bad news?
You looked at your phone lately?
No.
Capa and some of the other boys
have taken to Twitter
to demand we have our licence revoked.
They even started
an anti-SIM driver campaign.
Several of the other teams have jumped
on the bandwagon
and are independently
launching cases against us.
Gotta be kidding me.
Could that work?
Let's face it, it doesn't make it easy
for our sponsor to keep carrying us.
Nissan is considering shutting us down.
So...
We gotta prove to them, we gotta prove
to everyone, that we belong.
How?
By placing on the podium at Le Mans
with a team of SIM drivers.
I'm sorry. You're serious?
Le Mans. You...
- Podium at Le Mans.
- Yeah.
I mean, first thing is,
we'd need two other drivers.
Matty and Antonio, they've both
been racing the lower circuits
since GT Academy.
I mean, they can do it.
I believe in you, Jann.
You've driven this
a thousand times before in the game.
You can do this in your sleep.
You've done some amazing things, kid.
But Le Mans is...
It's a different animal.
It's the most physically demanding,
technically challenging race
in the entire world.
It's dangerous.
It tests you.
I couldn't do it.
But I know that you can.
Do you know that you can?
Let's be immortal.
We in?
Are you ready for it, Jann?
It's the big time, baby.
- Yo.
- How's it going?
Been watching the tour.
You look good, Stretch.
I don't feel so bad
for losing to you anymore.
Hey, man, look.
That wreck? It wasn't your fault.
We got your back.
I appreciate that.
- Thank you, man.
- Yeah, bro.
- Hey, guys.
- Are you boys ready for this?
This car...
it's a lot lighter, a lot faster
than the GT-Rs you've been driving.
It's quicker in the corners,
it requires more finesse, all right?
You gotta get the feel
or you'll lock up, you'll spin out.
Ah, whatever. You're gonna be fine.
With millions tuning in,
it's the 24 Hours of Le Mans,
the greatest race in the world.
Are you ready? I'm excited.
Good to see you, sir. How are you?
Ready.
Noobie.
Thank you for coming.
I...
I didn't support you properly.
I was trying to protect you. You know?
So many fathers, so many parents...
they have these kids
with these big, crazy dreams, you know?
And that damn PlayStation thing,
I just don't understand that shit, Jann.
I mean...
But, hey,
you did this.
I'm so goddamn proud of you.
I did this for you.
I'm proud of you.
I've got your back, my boy.
Just to go over it again,
it's a 24-hour race.
We start at 3 in the afternoon, daytime.
We race all night into the next day.
Race ends at 3.
We start with three-hour shifts
instead of the normal four.
Three, six, nine.
No driver in Le Mans can race
more than 14 hours.
I just wanna say something.
When he came to me and said
he was gonna start this GT Academy,
I thought all of you were completely nuts.
But you made me a believer.
Let's go show the world.
- These guys were in the Academy with Jann.
- Right. Hi.
- Hey, guys. This is Audrey.
- Hey.
- Hi!
- Hi. Nice to meet you. I'm Leah.
- Audrey.
Ladies and gentlemen, please rise
for the French national anthem.
The French Army has just arrived
to deliver the flag which will be used
to give the start of the Le Mans 24 Hours.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
Let's go.
One of the world's most iconic races,
the Le Mans 24,
stands just moments away
at the Circuit de la Sarthe.
And, Chenny, so many great stories
the length and breadth of this field,
but for me the one that's taking
my focus right now
is the incredible story at Nissan.
Is the last chance the SIM racers get
in professional motorsport?
There's an awful lot of pressure
on their shoulders.
Nobody wins this thing
on the first lap, okay?
You make your day, survive the night,
you live to fight tomorrow.
Good luck.
As the cars now leave the grid
for the formation lap
here at the Circuit de la Sarthe,
we are just moments away
from the start of this iconic race.
We're underway already and, listen,
you've gotta be smart going into turn one.
The tyres are still cold.
Contact! Contact in the back!
We've seen the BMW and the Aston Martin--
Okay, here we go.
Mulsanne Straight.
You could hit a high of 340 kph here.
You gotta build in enough time
to brake before chicane one.
Yes, yes. Okay.
I've done this a thousand times.
Well, not in reality.
Watch your speed.
Into the first chicane,
around the outside,
and it's a lovely move put on there
by Jann Mardenborough.
Watch those GT3s.
You're way faster than them.
I see Schulin.
Come on, Jann! Stay on him!
On your left!
Ferrari's too slow. Watch out!
No, no, no. No!
He gets tapped by the Ferrari!
Schulin up in the air!
Is he okay?!
What's he saying? Was it Jann?
Schulin! Get out, get out, get out!
Schulin climbs out of the car.
Making his way out, and that's good
to see from the fire marshals.
Safety car's out on the track.
Stay focused.
All right, they're pulling him out.
He seems all right. He seems all right.
After that impact,
it's a miracle the car is in one piece
and the driver could walk away.
Get behind that safety car.
Okay, keep your head in, all right? Focus.
All right, safety's out, race back on.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on!
Come on, you hear me?
Hey, buddy? Hey. Hey, Jann?
Hey, stay with me.
Stay with me, okay? Stay with me.
Look, safety's left, okay?
We gotta make up some time.
Jann.
Jann, talk to me, pal.
Jann. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Jann.
Is it a car problem
or is it a head issue, Will?
It would be early for anything
to be wrong with that car,
which has shown good pace.
Bitch.
Shit.
Jack!
We need to bring him in.
Then do something.
Just get his head back in this game.
Dude.
Dude, what the hell? Turn it off.
Turn it off!
Now! Turn it off!
Okay, let me just--
Oh, God, I don't know how to--
I told you,
I don't how to work these things.
Shit, Jack, turn it off now!
Shit.
Off.
You mad, bro?
Fucking yes!
Yes, I'm mad!
Yeah!
Well, get mad! It's about time!
Come on! Get in the fight!
I know you're scared.
I've been scared.
Whether you like it or not,
you are in this race.
So you take all that Kenny G anger
and you unleash it!
You hear me?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Go get 'em!
It's like he suddenly remembered
he was a racing driver.
Absolutely phenomenal display
by the debutante here in that Nissan.
All right, all right.
All right, coming up on Lotus.
Three seconds ahead.
Let's make up some ground.
You have the same power on the straight,
but if you get in the corner,
you'll be able to pass him, all right?
Okay, copy. Let me concentrate, old man.
Yeah, all right. Roger that. Copy.
Yes! Yes!
Beautiful stuff from Jann Mardenborough
and from this Nissan team.
Yes!
All right.
Now we only got 150 laps to go.
He pulled that first stint back,
and Jann Mardenborough into the pits
for the first driver change for Nissan.
Fast out there, man. Let's go, Matty!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Adiós!
As the sun goes down,
it's a whole new ballgame.
Don't rush it.
I'm gonna take the inside line, Jack.
- Yeah! Yes!
- Yo, son!
Yes!
- Maybe you boys can actually drive.
- You know we can drive.
Oh, yeah, jury's still out.
You're in P-9.
Get tyres ready. Here we go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
All leaders are on full wets.
Jann's doing great, isn't he?
- Do you think so?
- You joking? Mate, he's razing it!
I can't believe it. He's doing amazing.
Nice and softly, nice and smooth.
Hey, boys!
- How are you boys doing?
- Hey, man.
- Jann, how you feeling?
- I feel good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Rest up.
First light at Circuit de la Sarthe
at the 24 Hours of Le Mans.
Here you are, Audrey. Got you a coffee.
- Thanks.
- No worries.
How's it looking?
In fourth, but Antonio is losing ground.
Not a lot of time left.
Yeah,
Antonio Cruz clearly struggling there.
- Hey.
Antonio's cramping up.
We're gonna pit him early.
You ready to bring this home?
Let's go.
How we looking?
He's fallen back to fifth.
All right, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Get him in and get him out!
You. Check the radiator.
Come on, let's go!
Son, take a seat.
Change those tyres!
Come on, we're losing time!
Guys, what's going on?
- I dropped it!
- Oh, my God, what is happening?
Felix! What are you doing?
- Guys!
- Felix, come on! Where's the spare?
Damn it, we just lost our position.
What is happening?
- Where's the spare? Where's the spare?
- Are you shitting me?!
Oh, my God.
Come on!
Look at that, it's Jack Salter
who comes to the rescue.
- Always carry a spare.
- Sorry, sir.
How much did that hurt us?
We're running ninth, but...
You're on great pace.
Why don't you follow the race line?
You see, the other guys,
they follow that line.
So if I go wide like this,
sometimes I beat them.
Like that.
Jack, do you remember where this
whole GT Academy idea thing comes from?
Yeah, I'm listening.
The whole point of this thing was
to show that GT drivers can drive.
Okay? I know this track. I know the lines.
The line is not optimal.
Let me drive it my way.
- Now, wait a minute. The car won't hold.
- Wait, what's he saying?!
Yes, it will, Jack, okay?
I need you to trust me.
Do you trust me?
- Please go back to the box.
- What's happening?
- Jann! Listen.
- Get him out of here!
Just finish the race.
There's too much at stake.
It's too big of a risk.
- You cannot be here. Let's go.
- All right!
Danny, I didn't come here to finish.
Sir, this is your last warning.
I've got this, Danny.
- Don't push me, pal.
- Yeah.
You know what, fuck it.
Follow your line, Jann.
Come on.
- Holy shit!
- Yeah, Jann! Let's go!
That's six.
Five.
Four.
Come on, baby. Come on!
It's like he's got a cheat mode engaged.
He does. It's a new lap record!
Holy shit!
That's a new lap record for us!
No, no, no.
That's a new lap record, full stop.
Mardenborough is on a flyer.
And we're just shy of 24 hours completed.
We find ourselves now on the final lap.
You're P-4.
You're six seconds behind Capa.
You're only four seconds out
from standing on that podium.
- All right, you see him?
- Yes, I see him.
Defend your position.
Defend the podium.
Buckle up.
Don't try it, kid.
Last turn, then straight to the finish.
Come on, do your thing. Commit.
Commit!
Come on, punch it! Come on!
Here they come!
Within sight of the grandstands as well.
This is absolutely phenomenal.
- It is far from over, this race.
- Come on!
- He's gonna do it!
- Come on! Come on!
Yes! Yes!
It's Mardenborough! Mardenborough!
That is a phenomenal finish
to this year's 24 Hours of Le Mans!
- I cannot believe it.
- I am speechless.
Holy shit!
You did it!
Yes!
Listen, I will run your pit any day, noob.
There you are.
You're not just a SIM racer anymore.
You're one of the best in the world.